http://www.schaferandweiner.com/unique-firm/privacy-policy

Skip to main content area
Contact
|
Blog
A Unique FirmHow Schafer and Weiner Can HelpSpecializationApproachReputationTestimonials/Success StoriesPractice AreasRestructuringOut-of-Court WorkoutsCorporate BankruptcyPersonal BankruptcyUnsecured Creditors’ CommitteesCommercial LitigationCorporate Finance & TransactionsReal Estate DevelopmentTrusteesTeamThe S & W TeamPartnersDaniel J. WeinerMichael E. BaumHoward M. BorinJoseph K. GrekinKim K. HillaryJohn J. Stockdale, Jr.Jeffery J. SattlerAssociatesLeon N. MayerIn Memory of Arnold Schafer - 1948-2007News & KnowledgeBlogPublications by Schafer and WeinerNews & Events
How Schafer and Weiner Can Help
Specialization
Approach
Reputation
Testimonials/Success Stories
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us and maintaining your trust is our priority. To ensure that your privacy is protected, we provide this notice which explains our online information practices as well as the decisions you may make regarding how your information is collected and used.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Schafer & Weiner website. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to information connected online through our website and does not extend to information collected offline.
Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page in addition to updating the Privacy Policy modification date at the top.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you may contact us using the below information:
Solve this simple math problem and enter the result. E.g. for 1+3, enter 4.
The S&W Team
Publications by S&W
© Schafer & Weiner 2014  |  40950 Woodward Ave.  |  Suite 100  |  Bloomfield Hills, MI 48304  |  Phone: 248.540.3340  |  Sitemap  |  Privacy
